What are you wearing today? Ralph Lauren. You look phenomenal. Thank you.
Today is a Ralph Lauren day.
Just doing everything Ralph.
Even down to...
Down to the belt.
A little Ralph, just a little Ricky.
Something special for Pebble.
Something special for Pebble?
You're phenomenal. Thank you, you're phenomenal.
Your accessories.
All the accessories, just
gifts for my darling husband.
You're incredible.
And this necklace, come on.
Oh my God, thank you, thank you.
This was custom made.
What are you wearing today?
A Carolina Reda dress.
Gucci, the coat, and
Dolce & Gabbana, and Chanel.
Show us the arm.
Schiaparelli.
Yes, and this is
catchy.
And Schiaparelli earrings.
Let's see.
Amazing. Thank you.
Love your outfit.
Yes.
Love.
And your shoes?
Chanel. And the hat?
No brand.
What about the rings? We forgot about the rings.
Home hat and
pocari. Stunning.
Thank you so much. What are you wearing today?
Prada. Stunning.
And the bag.
And a hat from the Henry Ford Museum.
How about the bag?
The bag is vintage Chanel.
Stunning.
Chanel.
And the bag?
Is Schiaparelli. Stunning.
Tell us about the necklace.
The necklace is by a woman named
Zannie Sheik. She designs and produces
her own jewelry.
And the watch?
Cartier.
I can't miss the ring. Where's that from?
David Webb. Thank you so much.
You're welcome.